# Bartłomiej Cupiał

I am Machine Learning passionate. What drives me the most is to gain a better understanding of how intelligence and consciousness work, mainly by studying deep learning but recently also by neuroscience. My main areas of research is unsupervised and reinforcement learning, continual learning and improving the learning efficiency.



bartlomiej.cupial@gmail.com

505779373

Wrocław, Poland

in linkedin.com/in/username

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Wrocław University of Science and Technology**

MSc in Algorithmics

2020.03 - Present

#### **Wrocław University of Science and Technology**

**BSc in Computer Science** 

2016.10 - 2020.02

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Machine Learning Engineer**

- Responsible for design and implementation of machine learning based solutions for cardiac diagnostics problems.
- Used PyTorch, AzureML

2019.11 - Present

#### C++ developer in starter program Asseco

2019.07 - 2019.10

## **PROJECTS**

Machine Learning analysys of network simulations (2020.02 - Present)

- The goal of the project is to break Mix Network with DL.
- Research project
- Using Flax, AzureML

#### My Engineering Thesis (2019)

- Topic: Methods of camera recognition based on image samples
- Used machine learning methods

Reinforcement Learning for pong game (2019.10)

- Small project created especially for demonstration in DAS
- Used PyTorch, openai gym

My own implementation mix match algorithm (2019.06)

Used PyTorch and fastai

# **SKILLS**

Pvthon

NumPy, Pandas, PyTorch, Fastai



Git

STL, Boost, SFML



Linux

	$\bigcirc$	(

Docker

# **ORGANIZATIONS**

Solvro Students' Association (2018 – Present)

## **LANGUAGES**

**Polish** English B2/C1 Native

# ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

Conducting workshops for new people insterested in machine learning in Solvro Students' Association

MLinPL students speaker (2019 Conference) Talk about MixMatch

Fastai course by n-weaves

Participation in few kaggle contests

Hopelt Hackaton

## INTERESTS

Machine and Deep Learning

Chess

Basketball

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process under the Personal Data Protection Act as of 29 August 1997, consolidated text: Journal of Laws 2016, item 922 as amended.